go2arena.com 2017-02-17

# Privacy policy - G2A.COM

G2A.COM Limited, and from time to time, its subsidiaries (together the “Group”) (and each being “G2A.COM”, “we”, “us” or “member of the Group” for the purposes of this Privacy Policy as appropriate) recognise their responsibilities in relation to the collection, holding, processing, use and/or transfer of personal data under the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (Cap. 486) (“PDPO”). Personal data will be collected only for lawful and relevant purposes and all practicable steps will be taken to ensure that personal data held by us is accurate. We will use your personal data which we may from time to time collect in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

We regularly review this Privacy Policy and may from time to time revise it or add specific instructions, policies and terms. Where any changes to this Privacy Policy are material, we will notify you using the contact details you have provided us with and, where required by the PDPO, we will give you the opportunity to opt out of these changes by means notified to you at that time. Otherwise, in relation to personal data supplied to us through the G2A.COM website or otherwise, continued use by you of the G2A.COM website, or other products or services of the Group, or your continued relationship with us or the Group shall be deemed to be your acceptance of and consent to this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or how we use your personal data, please contact us through one of the communication channels set out in the “Contact Us” section below. 

G2A.COM will take all practicable steps to ensure the security of your personal data and to avoid unauthorised or accidental access, erasure or other use of your personal data. This includes physical, technical and procedural security methods, where appropriate, to ensure that your personal data may only be accessed by authorised personnel.  

Please note that if you do not provide us with your personal data (or relevant personal data relating to persons appointed by you to act on your behalf) we may not be able to provide the information, products or services you have asked for or be able to process your requests.

**Purpose**

From time to time we may collect your personal data including but not limited to your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, date of birth and login name for the following purposes: 

  1. to process your transaction, subscriptions and registration for our products and services;

  2. to process your transaction, subscriptions and registration for products and services of third-parties;

  3. to provide you with our products and services and administer your account in relation to such products and services;

  4. to provide you information about our Group products and services;

  5. to provide you information about relevant third-party products and services;

  6. to conduct research and statistical analysis; 

  7. to process your application for employment or engagement within G2A.COM to assess your suitability as a candidate for such position and to conduct reference checks with your previous employers; and

  8. other purposes related to any of the above.

**Direct Marketing**

Where you have given your consent and have not subsequently opted out, we may also use your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address to send promotional materials to you and conduct direct marketing activities in relation to G2A.COM products and services, and products services offered by other members of the Group, or products and services offered by relevant third-parties. 

If you do not wish to receive any promotional and direct marketing materials or do not wish to receive specific types of promotional and direct marketing materials or do not wish to receive such materials through a specific means of communication, please contact us through one of the communication channels set out in the “Contact Us” section below. To ensure that your request can be processed please provide your full name, email address, log in name and details of the product and/or service you have used.  

**Identifying Documentation**

We may also collect your identity card number, passport or other documentation pursuant to your use of our products and services as this may be required: under applicable laws or regulations, by regulators having authority over us and, subject to the PDPO, for the purpose of identifying you where it is reasonable for your identity card number to be used for this purpose.

**Transfer of Data**

Except to the extent you have already opted out we may transfer your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address to other members of the Group or relevant third-parties, for the purpose of enabling those members of the Group or relevant third-parties to send promotional materials to you and conduct direct marketing activities in relation to their products and services.

For one or more of the purposes specified above, your personal data may be: 

  1. transferred to other members of the Group, in Hong Kong or elsewhere and you consent to the transfer of your data outside of Hong Kong; 

  2. supplied to any agent, contractor or third party who provides administrative, telecommunications, computer, payment, debt collection, data processing or other services to G2A.COM and/or any member of the Group in Hong Kong or elsewhere; and

  3. other parties as notified to you at the time of collection.

**How We Use Cookies**

If you access our information or services through the G2A.COM website, you should be aware that cookies are used. Cookies are data files stored on your browser. The G2A.COM website automatically installs and uses cookies on your browser when you access it.

Cookies are used for the following purposes:

  1. To create statistics that help us understand how you access G2A.COM, which allows us to improve the structure of G2A.COM and its content and thus improve your experience;

  2. Creating a profile for you in order to display matching materials in regard to advertising networks, such as the Google Display Network;

  3. To run statistics on traffic to reliably conduct settlements with advertising partners;

  4. To store your settings and customize the Site to better suit your needs and preferences; and

  5. To recognize users of G2A.COM and the persons recommended by them within the framework of the Goldmine Marketing Programme. 

To achieve the above goals, the Site uses two basic types of cookies, session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are temporary files that are stored in your browser until you logout, leave the website or close the browser. Persistent cookies are stored in your browser for a longer period of time, as specified in the parameters of the cookie or until you remove the cookie. 

Cookies may be used by partners and advertising networks, such as the Google Display Network to display ads specific to you and in accordance your preferences while using G2A.COM. To achieve this goal cookies may store information about your navigation path or the time you spent on G2A.COM. To see what information was collected about you by the Google Display Network, you can view and edit the information derived from cookies with the following tool provided by Google: [https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/ ](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

Your browser’s default setting is likely set to allow for the storage of cookies. You can change your browser’s settings and delete or prevent cookies. For details, consult your browser’s documentation. Please note that if you do so you may not be able to utilise or activate certain functions available on G2A.COM.

**Legal Compliance**

G2A.COM and other members of the Group may be required to retain, process and/or disclose your personal data in order to comply with applicable laws and regulations or in order to comply with a court order, subpoena or other legal process, whether in Hong Kong or elsewhere, or to comply with a request by a government authority, law enforcement agency or similar body, whether in Hong Kong or elsewhere. G2A.COM and other members of the Group may need to disclose your personal data in order to enforce any agreement with you, protect our rights, property or safety, or the rights, property or safety of our employees.

**Access and Correction of Personal Data**

Under the PDPO, you have the right to verify whether we hold your personal data, to obtain a copy of the data, and to correct any data that is inaccurate. You may also request us to inform you of the type of personal data held by us. All data access requests shall be made using the form prescribed by the Privacy Commissioner for Personal Data (“ **Privacy Commissioner** ”) which may be found on the official website of the Office of the Privacy Commissioner or via this link: [https://www.pcpd.org.hk/english/publications/files/Dforme.pdf ](https://www.pcpd.org.hk/english/publications/files/Dforme.pdf)

Requests for access and correction of personal data or for information regarding policies and practices and the kinds of data held by us should be addressed in writing and sent by post to us (see the “Contact Us” section below). 

A reasonable fee may be charged to offset our administrative and actual costs incurred in complying with your data access requests.

**Termination or Cancellation**

Should your account or relationship with us be cancelled or terminated at any time, we shall cease processing your personal data as soon as reasonably practicable following such cancellation or termination, provided that we may keep copies of your data as is reasonably required for archival purposes, for use in relation to any actual or potential dispute, for the purpose of compliance with applicable laws and regulations and for the purpose of enforcing any agreement we have with you, for protecting our rights, property or safety, or the rights, property or safety of our employees, and for performing or discharging our functions, obligations and responsibilities.

**General**

If this Privacy Policy is translated into any other language, and there is any inconsistency or conflict between the English and translated versions of this Privacy Policy, the English version shall prevail.

**Contact us**

By Post:

PDPO

**G2A.COM Limited**

36/F, Tower Two, 

Times Square, 

1 Matheson Street, 

Causeway Bay, 

Hong Kong

By Email:

PDPO@G2A.COM.COM
